There are many monsters threatening humans
我等居住的广大世界
in the vast world where we live.
有许多怪物 威胁着人类
Many adventurers and heroes
挺身而出的是 众多的冒险家
stepped forward bravely.
以及勇者们
They face many dangerous challenges today
他们为了保护人们 保护世界
to protect the people and the world.
今天也面对许多危险的挑战
And I, Alvin, is one of them.
而我埃尔文 就是其中一位
I'm going to encounter a monster.
马上就遇到怪物啦
All right. Take this.
好 看我的吧
THE TITLE
(此次的标题)
ALVIN (MALE LEAD/ARMORED WARRIOR), WHO IS TRYING TO BE AN ADVENTURER
(在充斥着魔物和怪物的世界 尝试着成为一名冒险家的埃尔文)
IN A WORLD FULL OF DEMONS AND MONSTERS, IS FIGHTING WITH A BEAR.
((男主角/盔甲战士) 正与熊怪战斗)
FORTUNATELY, Carla (FEMALE LEAD/DARK ELF), A DARK ELF HEALER, HAPPENED TO PASS BY
(遇到危机之时幸运地 有位黑暗精灵僧侣卡菈)
WHEN HE WAS IN DANGER. Carla'S CHARACTER IS VERY GOOD AT DEBATE.
((女主角/黑暗精灵) 正好路过卡菈的性格十分擅长辩论)
THE BEAR WAS CONFUSED. THERE'S EVEN A PLOT THAT DOESN'T EXIST IN THE COMIC.
(连熊怪都感到困惑 甚至出现回熊怪家)
THEY WENT BACK TO THE BEAR'S HOUSE. THE COMIC FANS WILL BE WONDERING.
(漫画里没有的剧情 原作粉定会不自觉的「咦」出声音)
BUT THIS IS THE SAME WORLDVIEW STORY PUBLISHED ONLINE, "WHAT'S THIS STORY"
(但这是在杂志连载前 发表在网络上「这是什么故事」)
BEFORE THE MAGAZINE SERIAL. PLEASE UNDERSTAND THE INTENTION
(的相同世界观的故事 还请各位理解在此说明)
OF THE STAFF AND THE ORIGINAL AUTHOR. BESIDES, SUCH A LONG TITLE IS UNSUITABLE
(工作人员及原作方的用意 另外这么长的标题)
FOR STRAIGHT OR OBLIQUE SUBTITLES, SO IT'S NOT DONE.
(不论上成直的或斜的字幕 都不适合干脆就不做了)
Geez.
可恶
It has such lovely eyes, yet it's so strong.
有双这么可爱的眼睛 却强到不像话
OF FIRST EPISODE
(的第1话)
Oh, no.
糟糕
I'm doomed.
完蛋了
Excuse me. Are you in trouble?
请问 你遇到困难了吗
Nice to meet you. I'm Carla,
初次见面你好 我是僧侣
a dark elf healer.
黑精灵的卡菈
Thank you for introducing yourself precisely.
谢谢你细心地自我介绍
I'm a human, Alvin.
我是人类埃尔文
I'm kind of... a warrior...
算是一位…战士…
But it's not the time to introduce myself.
但现在不是自我介绍的时候
Are you all right?
你还好吗
Do I look all right?
我看起来还好吗
Don't just stand there. Help me.
别杵在那 快帮我啊
When you ask someone a favor,
有求于人的时候
isn't it necessary to kneel and kowtow?
跪下来磕头不是基本的吗
I'm sorry. Wait a minute.
抱歉 等我一下
Huh, what's wrong?
咦 怎么了吗
People will usually help at this time.
这种时候通常都会帮忙吧
Why should I kneel and kowtow?
为何要我跪下磕头啊
Why are you shouting so loudly?
你干嘛叫这么大声
Are you feeling stressed out?
压力太大了吗
I'm getting stressed out now.
我现在"正"压力大
Are you going to vent your anger on me as you're about to lose to the monster?
难道是快输给怪物 所以迁怒我
Please accept the fact that you're weak.
请接受自己很弱的事实
Shut up!
烦死了
You're yelling again.
又怒吼了
Humans are scary. Just die out.
人类好可怕 灭亡算了
There's no need to cry.
没必要哭吧
It's my bad for yelling at you.
对你怒吼是我不好
"My bad."
"不好"
You should say "I'm so sorry."
你应该要说"我很抱歉"吧
You…
你这…
No, I can't just listen to her.
不行 不能被她牵着鼻子走
I should calm down like a mature adult.
我要冷静 像个成熟的大人
What about your "I'm so sorry"?
你的"我很抱歉"呢
No, I'm going to lose my mind.
不行 理智线快断了
Oh no, I forgot it.
糟糕 我都忘了
Give me a few more minutes.
再等我一下
All right. How about this?
好 这样吧
You're Carla, right?
你叫做卡菈吧
If you're willing to help, I'll do you a favor.
若你愿意帮忙 我就如你所愿一件事
Anything will do?
什么事都可以吗
I'll try my best.
尽我所能
Then kneel and kowtow.
那就跪下磕头
Why are you persistent about this?
你对跪下磕头有什么执着啊
I wanted this, but forget it.
原本想要这个 但算了
In contrast, Mr. Alvin.
相对的 埃尔文先生
Please form a party with me.
请跟我组队
A party?
组队
Actually, I've never formed a party before.
其实 我从未组过队
I think so. It's hard for your character.
我想也是 你这种性格很难吧
No one seems to want to talk to me.
大家似乎都不想跟我说话
I may be the so-called "flower at the top of a tall mountain".
我可能是所谓的"高岭之花"吧
You should be "poisonous weeds in a swamp".
是"沼泽之毒草"吧
You really can't blink.
你真不会眨眼
It's okay to form a party.
要组队是可以啦
Thank you, Mr. Alvin.
谢谢你 埃尔文先生
It'll be dissolved soon, anyway.
反正马上就解除了
First of all, I'm an adventurer. But my level isn't high.
先说好 我虽然是冒险家 但等级并不高哦
Don't expect too much from me.
别对我期望过高
Okay. I expect nothing from you.
好的 我对你没有任何期望
Your action and speech are completely different.
动作和言语完全不同调
Don't give a thumbs up.
不要竖起大拇指
Anyway, please heal me quickly.
总之 快点帮我回复吧
The economy?
景气吗
My strength.
体力啦
Your strength?
回复体力
You've been yelling since just now. You should be very energetic.
你从刚才就一直大吼大叫的 应该很有精神啊
Watch your words.
你的措辞
I got it.
我知道了
You want to be spoiled, right?
你想撒娇吧
Could you hurry it up?
快点好不好
I wanted to lighten the atmosphere.
我本来想缓和气氛的说
Did you?
是哦
But you're not talented at it. Don't do so again.
但你没有这方面的才华 下次别这样了
All right, let's start.
那么 开始咯
What a nuisance.
麻烦死了
Dissolve when the fight is over.
战斗结束后就解散吧
Don't move.
别乱动
Your heart is still moving.
心脏还在动
If my heart stops, I'll die.
心脏停了就死了
Don't yell so loudly all of a sudden.
不要突然叫这么大声
I accidentally cursed you.
害我不小心下成诅咒了
It's you who…
是你…
What did you say?
你刚才说什么
I accidentally cursed you.
我不小心下成诅咒了
Bleh, hey.
呸嘿嘿
What kind of new healer put a curse?
下诅咒的僧侣是哪来的新职业啊
Don't worry. It's not a great curse.
别紧张 不是什么了不起的诅咒
Really?
真的吗
You'll die if you're 300 meters away from me.
离我300米远就会死
Die…
死…
Don't do so.
讨厌
Even if you're happy, you don't have to kneel before me.
就算你很开心也不用跟我跪下
It's strange for me.
这样我会觉得很怪
I'm going despair.
我要绝望了
What should I do?
怎么办
So we can't be separated?
这样我们不就分不开了吗
You're so mean. Were you just tricking me?
好过分 你对我只是玩玩的吗
I'm mad because I have to take it seriously.
就是不能只玩玩所以才气啊
Both of you, please calm down.
两位冷静点吼
Who's that?
谁
It's not good to fight, kuma.
吵架不好哦熊
Alvin, don't be so harsh to a girl, bear.
埃尔文 对女孩子别这么凶贝尔
Carla, you should think more about others' feelings, roar.
卡菈也要多考虑别人的心情吼
Since you two are a party, get along well, kuma.
既然都组队了 就好好相处吧熊
Talk nicely, bear.
好好聊聊贝尔
Okay? Roar.
好吗 吼
Don't talk like a human, okay?
别说人话好吗
And keep the auxiliary words at the end of the sentences consistent.
还有 句末语助词统一一下
Cursing each other is not the way. Let's have a good talk.
互相辱骂也不是办法 我们好好聊聊吧
The topic is about
议题是
a warrior looking down on a healer.
关于战士瞧不起僧侣一事
Sorry, I've got something to say since the beginning.
抱歉才刚开始我就有话说
I have an objection to this topic.
关于这个议题我有异议
And there's one more thing I care about.
另外有件事我也很在意
What is it, the defendant?
什么事 被告
My objection was approved.
异议被认同了
But let's put it aside.
但先把这件事放一边
Why did the monster join too?
为何魔兽也一同参与
I'm sorry to hear that.
真令人难过
Do you think the monster isn't qualified to join the discussion?
难道你觉得魔兽没资格参加讨论吗
No, we were fighting just now.
不 刚刚我们还在打架耶
That's so sad.
太难过了
The lives of monsters and humans are equal.
魔兽和人类的性命同等尊贵
Even though we look different, we should accept each other in the spirit of indiscriminate love.
即便外表不同 也该以博爱的精神接纳彼此
So we can understand each other.
如此定能互相理解
Don't be like you remember you're a healer suddenly, okay?
可以不要像是突然想起 自己的职业是僧侣好吗
Excuse me, kuma.
打扰一下熊
Do you want to say something?
你要发言吗
I heard that the longer a monster lives, the wiser it will be.
我听说魔兽 活得越长久就越有智慧
And it has rich experience.
并拥有丰富的经验
If it's a dragon, I can understand that.
如果是龙族的话我还能理解
Before you express your opinion, may I have your name, please?
在你阐述意见之前 请问你叫什么名字
I'm so sorry.
真是不好意思吼
But our race doesn't have the "name" mentioned by humans, kuma.
不过我们的种族 并没有人类所说的"名字"熊
Even if it has wisdom, it still can't keep the end of the sentences consistent.
就算拥有智慧 但句末语助词还是无法统一
But humans call us
不过人类都称呼我们种族为
Oomune bears, bear.
大宗熊贝尔
It's too random.
太随便了吧
Mr. Oomune Bear, do you have any idea?
大宗熊先生有什么想法吗
Oh right, kuma.
对哦熊
From your dialogue just now, it's what I think.
刚才听你们的对话我觉得
First of all, Carla.
首先是卡菈
Carla's occupation is a healer. It's easily to be targeted, kuma.
卡菈的职业是僧侣 是很容易被当成目标的职业熊
The only occupation that can protect you is warrior.
能保护你的 只有战士这个职业
If the warrior collapses, you'll also be in danger.
若战士倒下 你也会有危险
Carla, you're smart.
卡菈是个聪明的人
You should be clear about what to do, right?
该怎么做 应该很清楚吼吧
And the defendant Alvin.
再来是被告埃尔文
The defendant…
被告…
Although you were in the fight,
虽然在战斗中
you blurted out a lot of verbal violence.
但你脱口而出的众多言语暴力
Does its subtext convey an arrogant message
其潜台词是否传达了
like "even if it's the first meeting" and "a healer should restore strength
"就算是初次见面" "僧侣理当为战士回复体力"
for a warrior", kuma?
如此傲慢的信息熊
The elves are very sensitive to people's negative emotions.
精灵族对人的负面情绪十分敏感吼
Carla maybe unknowingly felt these emotions, bear.
或许在不知不觉中 卡菈早已感受到这些情绪贝尔
I said so much, roar.
说了这么多吼
I mainly hope that since you've formed a party,
主要是希望你们既然组队了
you two are important to each other.
双方都是彼此重要的存在
Besides, Alvin can't stay more than 300 meters away from Carla.
更何况埃尔文以后 不能离卡菈超过300米
You two should learn to respect and tolerate each other in daily life, kuma.
我觉得两位在日常生活中 应学会互相尊重包容熊
So that's a monster that can speak like a human.
不愧是会说人话的魔兽
Since it has lived for such a long time,
活了这么长的岁月
its words are persuasive.
说出来的话语十分有说服力
You.
你啊
It's saying something convincing. Yet, you're dozing off.
人家正说的如此有道理 你竟然在打瞌睡
I didn't doze off.
我没睡啊
You did.
你睡了吧
Don't you know the "sleep learning method"?
难道 你不知道"睡眠学习法"吗
You just fell asleep.
就是睡着了啊
Sit down!
给我坐下
- What do you want? - Just sit down!
-要干嘛 -反正给我坐下
What's wrong with you since just now?
你从刚才是怎样
You simply cursed people. And there's something wrong with your attitude.
随便诅咒人就算了 你的态度超有问题
Calm down, kuma.
冷静点熊
No. To deal with such a person, you have to scold her severely.
不 对付这种人 就是要狠很地骂他一顿
All right, roar.
好了好了吼
You dozed off while someone else was talking. That's so rude of you.
人家在说话时你打瞌睡 太没礼貌了吧
All right, kuma.
好了好了熊
You can only do that when the headmaster is giving a speech.
只有在校长致词时 才能这么做
All right. You can't do so at that time too, bear.
好了好了 那时也不行贝尔
What about the congressman?
那国会议员呢
It's even more unforgivable to doze off at a national meeting.
开国家会议时打瞌睡 更是不可原谅
You also can't do that when the headmaster is giving a speech, kuma.
校长致词时也不行哦熊
By the way, what are we talking about now, bear?
话说 现在到底在说什么贝尔
This monster has lived for a long time, right?
这只魔兽 活了很久对吧
Well…
请问…
That means it's an elder.
也就是说 它是长辈
"DARK ELF FEMALE 72 YEARS OLD" You should respect it.
(黑暗精灵 雌 72岁) 应该要尊敬人家
"ABOUT 14-15 YEARS OLD OF HUMAN AGE" Right?
(约人类的14 15岁) 对吧
"OOMUNE BEAR MALE 324 YEARS OLD" You should treat
(大宗熊 雌 324岁) 要温柔
"ABOUT 43-44 YEARS OLD OF HUMAN AGE" the elderly gently.
(约人类的43 44岁) 对待老人家
"HUMAN MALE 30 YEARS OLD" Treat older men
(人类 雄 30岁) 好好对待
"WARRIOR LEVEL 7-8 YEARS OLD" and older women well.
(战士等级 7 8岁) 老爷爷老奶奶
How…
怎…
How can you gossip about a lady's age, kuma?
怎么能对淑女的年龄说三道四熊
My legs…
我的脚…
Paralysis.
麻痹
It's paralysis, not paradise.
是麻痹不是乐园
Oh no, kuma.
不好了熊
What should I do?
怎么办吼
Oh, well…
这个那个吼…
Kuma!
熊
Now you know the power of the monster, bear.
知道魔兽的厉害了吧贝尔
My legs are numb and painful.
脚麻了好痛苦
I'm collapsing.
我倒
I seemed to have encountered something scary.
我好像遇到非常可怕的事
What a relief. You wake up, bear.
太好了 你醒来了贝尔
I just came back from picking oranges, kuma.
我刚好摘了橙果回来熊
Eat the orange to recover your strength, roar.
吃下橙果 恢复体力吧吼
Thank you.
谢谢
It tastes good.
好好吃
Is this your home?
这里是你家吗
Yes, it's my den, roar.
对 是我的巢穴吼
Den…
巢穴…
But it's great, bear.
不过真是太好了贝尔
You were injured badly that you almost died, kuma.
你的伤严重到差点死掉熊呢
I beat you, though, roar.
虽然 是我打的吼
So you're a female.
原来 你是女的
Sorry for being rude.
抱歉 我说了许多失礼的话
I'm the one to apologize, bear.
我才要道歉呢贝尔
Did you save me?
是你救了我吗
It's not me, kuma.
不是我熊哦
She seems sorry for you.
她好像对你有点过意不去吼
She has been casting recovery magic on you to help you heal.
一直对你施展回复魔法 帮你疗伤
Recovery magic?
回复魔法
Is it morning?
早上了吗
I want bread for breakfast.
早餐我要吃面包
Add lots of sugar and milk to the coffee.
咖啡里要加很多糖和牛奶
Add honey to the yogurt.
优格要加蜂蜜
You demand so much.
你的要求真多
Are you dressing up like that?
你的打扮 是那个吧
"IT IS JUST AN IMPRESSION" Put a five-inch nail on the doll
(这只是印象) 在人偶上钉五吋钉
"IT IS DIFFERENT FROM WHAT Carla ACTUALLY DID" to curse others.
(与卡菈实际做的事相异) 诅咒对方
Your injury is too severe. It's not enough to cast recovery magic just once.
你的伤太重 只施展一次回复魔法还不够
She tried her best to cast many times.
她很努力的施展了很多次吼
There are too many five-inch nails.
五吋钉的数量太多了吧
It's like magic needle therapy.
好像是咒术针治疗法
Your wound should have been healed, bear.
你的伤应该好了贝尔
It's all thanks to Carla, kuma.
这都是卡菈的功劳熊
Although I'm okay now…
虽然现在没问题…
I don't get it.
但我想不通
Breakfast…
早餐…
It seems that she cried as she felt relieved.
看来 她安心地哭了呢
$^%@*&
$^%@*&
She cried until uttering nonsense.
哭到胡言乱语了
Sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry.
对不起 对不起sorry
Why do you repeat it?
干嘛重说一次
I tried very hard to use recovery magic.
我很努力地使用回复魔法
But your injury is too severe.
可是你的伤势过重
Your body is finally cured.
好不容易治好身体
But your face is still miserable…
但脸还是很惨…
Your words… Miserable face.
你的措辞… 脸很惨
The wound on your face is severe. I think at least return to your proper appearance.
脸上的伤真的很严重 我想说至少回复应有的样貌
Plastic surgery…
整型吗…
I tried to recover you back to your original appearance.
我努力回复到接近原本的样貌
But I don't know why
但不知道为什么
it turned out looking ugly.
却是一副不怎么样的长相
Was I dissed?
我被羞辱了吗
No, she didn't diss you.
不 她并不没有羞辱你滴
Are you bullying me together?
现在是在联合欺负我吗
Why did the auxiliary word at the end of the sentence change?
你的句末语助词怎么变了
Your face is really miserable, kuma.
脸真的很惨熊
It's too late to save it.
努力挽救也来不及了吼
Your words.
你的措辞
Please use this, bear.
请用这个贝尔
You have a hand mirror.
你有手镜啊
It's a girl's habit, kuma.
少女的嗜好嘛熊
A monster's habit...
魔兽的嗜好…
Well, the wound on my face can't be cured...
这样啊 脸上的伤无法痊愈啊…
I'm sorry. Sorry.
对不起 sorry
Do you like this method of making an apology very much?
你很喜欢这种道歉方法吗
It's too serious to be treated…
严重到无法挽救…
It doesn't feel different touching it…
摸起来并没有特别的感觉…
What?
什么
Kuma.
熊
Please don't hate Carla, bear.
请不要恨卡菈贝尔
She tried her very best to recover your original appearance.
她很努力让你恢复原本的长相
But her magic power wasn't enough.
但魔力不够
That's why your look is semi-finished, bear.
所以才会变成半成品的模样贝尔
Carla, don't cry, roar.
卡菈 不要哭吼
Come to think of it. I haven't seen Mr. Alvin's face before.
仔细想想 我没看过埃尔文先生的长相
It's not your fault, bear.
你没有错贝尔
Just hate me if you want.
要恨就恨我
Just hate me, kuma.
恨我这只魔兽吧熊
- Roar… - No, it's completely recovered.
-吼吼吼… -不 完全恢复原状了啊
I'm used to being hated by humans, kuma.
我习惯被人类怨恨了熊
It's all my fault, roar.
都是我的错吼
No, it's me. I don't have enough power.
是我 是我力量不够
I just said it. It has recovered to its original state.
就说了 恢复原状了
I even look good.
甚至连脸色都很好
I just said it.
就说了
It has completely recovered to my original appearance.
完全恢复原本的长相了
That's great. You're awake.
太好了 你醒了
I've been awake long ago.
很早就醒了
Are you going to act as nothing happened?
你打算当作什么都没发生过吗
You've been injured so badly.
你受了这么重的伤
This is a miracle indeed.
这简直是神迹啊
What do you mean by looking ugly?
不怎么样的长相是什么意思
God, you're amazing. VIVA GOD.
神啊 太厉害了 VIVA GOD
What's a semi-finished look?
半成品的模样是什么
I'm amazing, too. VIVA Carla.
我也好厉害 VIVA 卡菈
Roar.
吼
I'll put the cape here, roar.
我把披风放在这吼
Thank you.
谢谢
You have a lot of equipment.
你有好多装备哦
I used to be young, kuma.
以前 我也曾年轻过嘛熊
I fought with many adventurers at that time, bear.
当时 我跟许多冒险家打过架贝尔
These are the spoils of war, roar.
这些都是当时的战利品吼
It seems that as you grow older, you'll become tactful...
看来随着年龄增长 个性也会变圆…
I... I mean... The big city is still far away.
我我我…我是说…大都市还很远
Alvin is such a sensible human, kuma.
埃尔文是个懂事的人类熊
I'm sure you can get along well with Carla, roar.
一定能跟卡菈相处得很好吼
I have no confidence in this.
关于这点我完全没有自信
You can do it, bear.
加油贝尔
It's easy to hold.
好顺手哦
I'll punish you in the name of God.
我要代替神惩罚你
Holy Beam.
神圣光束
ALVIN'S CAPE
(埃尔文的披风)
Are you two going to leave, bear?
你们真的要走了吗贝尔
Yes.
是啊
Don't go in such a hurry, kuma.
不用这么急着走熊嘛
It's fate to meet each other.
相遇就是缘分
Stay here tonight, bear.
今晚就住下来吧贝尔
That won't work.
那可不行
I'm a human, you're a monster.
我是人类 你是魔兽
It's strange for us to get along well.
相处融洽是件很奇怪的事
That's right, roar…
也是吼…
First of all.
先说好
I'm very competitive.
我的好胜心很强
The attack came unprepared, but I won't lose all the time.
虽然此次攻击来得措手不及 但我不会一直输下去的
Bear.
贝尔
I'll challenge you again in the near future.
近期 我会再来找你挑战的
Get ready to welcome me.
做好准备等着欢迎我吧
Do you get it?
知道吗
Roar. Roar.
吼 吼
Kuma! Kuma...
熊 熊熊熊…
Human, you're pretty powerful, roar.
你这个人类挺有气势的嘛吼
Okay. I'll give you a grand welcome, bear.
好 到时我会盛大欢迎你贝尔
Don't forget by then.
到时可别忘了
And remember to keep the auxiliary words at the end of the sentences consistent.
还有 记得统一句末语助词
Stop it.
别再说了
You scared me, kuma.
吓死熊了吼
Huh? What's wrong?
干嘛 怎么了
What do you think?
什么怎么了
Why... Why do you have to fight?
为何 为何要起纷争呢
Why? You get along well with each other.
为什么 好不容易变得这么要好
Well, kuma…
那个熊…
Why did you make a promise to come back and challenge?
为何还做了要回来挑战的约定
- No, it's the atmosphere. - No, it's the atmosphere, roar.
-不不不 这是气氛 气氛 -不不不 这是气氛 气氛吼
I thought monsters and humans could live in peace.
我原以为魔兽和人类能和平相处
No, you know it, right?
不 你懂的吧
It's just a matter of principle.
这只是个大原则问题
Look at the atmosphere, okay?
你看一下气氛好吗
Why can't you stop hating and hurting each other?
为何就不能停止互相憎恨 互相伤害呢
That's not it.
不是啦
Actually, we have a good relationship.
实际上我们感情很好
But we deliberately sounded hostile.
但只是故意说得好像是敌对
Do I have to explain it? It's so embarrassing.
我非说明不可吗 超不好意思的
Don't beat around the bush!
不要跟我顾左右而言他
Oomune Bear brought the injured you here.
大宗熊把受伤的你搬来这里
She's your savior. No, she's your life-saving bear.
她算是你的救命恩人 不对 是救命恩熊
You should be grateful to her.
你应该要好好感谢她
By the way, I cured your serious injury.
话又说回来 我治好你的重伤
I'm the one who contributed the most.
算是最有功劳的人
Things happened for a reason.
虽说事出有因
But you should pay tribute to those who worked hard.
但对努力之人 应该要给予感恩的敬意吧
Of course, that's not why I chose this occupation.
我当然不是为此 才选择这个职业
If all can always say the words of gratitude,
若大家都能经常说出感恩的词汇
I'll gladly accept your regard.
我也会欣然接受大家的心意
All in all, I gladly accept this wand.
总而言之 我欣然接受这支权杖
I gladly accept it.
我欣然接受
"GIVE ME A REWARD" Thanks.
(给我奖励) 谢啦
You really got the wand.
结果 真的得到权杖了
Of course, I deserve it.
那当然 这是我应得的报酬
You took it shamelessly.
应该是厚颜无耻的拿走吧
Forget it.
算了
How long will the curse last that I'll die if I leave you?
我离开你身边就会死的诅咒 会维持多久
Isn't there a way to dispel it?
没有解除方法吗
Your way of expression is very infuriating.
你的表达方式真的很令人火大
Your every move makes me mad.
一举一动都很火大
I have to be with you all the time…
之后还要一直跟你在一起哦…
Yes. I don't want to, though.
是啊 虽然很不愿意
It's me who doesn't want it.
不愿意的是我吧
There's no other choice.
没办法了
Since you saved me, I'd do you a favor. Do you still remember it?
你救了我我就听你一个要求 你还记得吧
Yes.
记得
You saved me from serious injury.
你救了受重伤的我
I'll do you a favor.
我就听你的要求吧
Let's form a party.
我们组队吧
I look forward to working with you.
请多指教
Me... Me too.
彼…此彼此
It hurts!
好痛
Well, it's…
这是那个…
It's a pity that you couldn't
没能握到女孩子的手
hold a girl's hand.
真可惜
What did you say?
你说什么
I spoke your mind. Are you yelling to cover it up?
被人说中心声 就用大吼大叫来掩盖吗
It's even troublesome to prove my innocence.
连要证明自己的清白也好麻烦
Bleh, hey.
呸嘿嘿
DON'T HURT ME, MY HEALER
(这个僧侣有够烦)
Mistur Alvin.
埃尔文先森
What's the matter, Misu Carla?
什么事 卡菈小节
Where are we going to stay tonight?
今天晚上在哪住宿
It'll be dawn when we get to the city.
走到城市时就天亮了吧
What should we do?
怎么办呢
Miss Oomune Bear has invited you to stay.
大宗熊小姐都邀请你住下了
You.
你啊
I was acting cool. How could I ask to stay?
当时都耍帅成那样 哪还能要求住下啊
It's too embarrassing to go back now.
现在回去也太丢脸了
Mr. Alvin.
埃尔文先生
What's the matter?
干嘛
I feel the pain again that
我重新身痛欲绝的感受到
you're really clumsy.
你真的很笨拙耶
Can't you retort it?
无法反驳吗
Bingo.
宾果
Congratulations, you got it right.
恭喜你猜对了
You have me now.
现在有我跟着你啊
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
放心交给我吧
"NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW" Title of the next episode.
(下集预告) 下集的标题
"ACCIDENTALLY FELL INTO GOBLINS' TRAP AND MADE TEAMMATE A EXHAUSTED" Alvin, who was on the journey
(又不小心中了哥布林的陷阱 害A队友累个半死) 和僧侣卡菈
"THE CURSE HASN'T BEEN LIFTED, SO CAN'T SEPARATE FROM Carla" with the healer Carla, wanted to collect detoxifying grass
(但诅咒尚未解除 所以不能跟卡菈分开) 一同踏上旅程的埃尔文
"I THINK I'LL BE EXHAUSTED. AND SUCH A LONG TITLE CONTAINS" for some purpose but fought with ghosts
(觉得自己以后都会累得像狗一样 而这么长的标题) 因某个目的要收集解毒草
"THE NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW. HOW MANY PEOPLE WILL LISTEN TO THE END?" in the cemetery on the way. Just when
(其实还包含了下集预告内容 但能听到最后的人又有多少) 却在途中的墓地里和幽灵战斗
"CAN'T WAIT FOR EPISODE TWO""STAY TUNED" they'll solve the crisis in an inexplicable way…
(真是让人好奇啊的第2话)(要继续观看哦) 正当以为用莫名的方法解除危机时…